trainright.com 2006-06-25

# Carmichael Training Systems - Coaches and Camps for Cycling, Multisport, Running, and Aerobic | Privacy Policy

**Thank You For Visiting CTS**

This privacy policy tells you how CTS uses personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. We may, infrequently, change these practices, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Depending on what you do when you visit any web site, you are providing information about your visit to the site's owners. This includes CTS. We value privacy and know you do too, so we want you have an understanding of what our privacy policies are relative to information you may supply to the CTS web site.

The bottom line at CTS is that we use the information that we get from your visit for internal tracking purposes, to make trainright.com as useful and interesting to you as we can, and to respond to your requests for information or other services. Except as specifically noted, we do not use your personal information for any other purpose; we never sell it to any third party; and, we never share it with any third party.

**What personal information we collect and how we use your information:**

When you visit the CTS web site, we capture the internet provider's domain name and country that you came from (e.g., 'aol.com') and the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e., your "click stream" activity).

Information we collect on trainright.com may be used to enhance your use of this web site in ways like these: 

  * Arrange the web site in the most user-friendly way 
  * Customize your browsing experience of this web site 
  * Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices 
  * Respond to your question or suggestions 

_Visitor Registration or Requests for Information_  
"Personal information" includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address. While you can browse our site without registering, you will need to register in order to take advantage of certain features, such as requesting the CTS Newsletter and updates, or promotional offers we may offer.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology:**

The Site uses cookie and tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. The Site uses cookies and other tracking technology for these purposes and to make sure you don't see the same information repeatedly. We record information on site traffic but not information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used.

To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)

**How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us:**

If you choose to receive them, CTS may periodically send you email messages describing updates, new features, or promotional offers related to this web site. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time. Simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request.

If you do not explicitly choose to receive informational emails, the only email messages you will receive from CTS will be to respond to email inquiries that you send us.

**How we protect the security of your personal information:**

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. CTS uses firewalls and has security measures in place at its physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our web site. Only authorized CTS employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

**How to contact CTS**

Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any CTS related service, you consent to CTS’s processing of this information in the United States as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating.

If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about the CTS privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to contact us.
